placestoseeinyourlifetime.com 2014-04-13

# Privacy policy | Places To See In Your Lifetime

**Personal information privacy**

It’s in our best interest to make browsing in our website easy and comfortable for our users and we seek to make a management of your private data and information would be easy and transparent.

Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com may collect your personal information, such as name, surname, e-mail address and use it for ordering and delivering goods or services, also, after given your personal approval, for other defined matters. Demographic data, such as sex or age, could be used in purpose of improving our website by adapting it to needs and requests of users.

While managing personal data of our users, we reserve the right to disclose it only in cases when it is necessary for delivering ordered goods or services. We do not publish or in any other way disclose personal data of users to the third parties, except the cases when disclosing personal data is obliged by law.

Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com is not responsible for your personal information and data that is used in websites of the third parties. Also Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com isn’t responsible for any cases when user is led to other websites by clicking on links in Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com. We suggest users to read privacy policy of websites belonging to the third parties.

**The purpose of cookies**

In Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com cookies are used for purposes of statistics, aiming to evaluate popularity of separate segments or pages of the website (as well as for carrying analysis of statistics). Also cookies allow users to navigate the website easier and allow us to provide more concrete information to users. This type of information management does not in any way disclose user’s personality.

User is capable of removing cookies from his/her computer by using web browser. Warning: some of our services might not work properly after blocking cookies.  
Placestoseeinyourlifetime.com reserves the right to provide third parties with anonymous statistical information.
